kapwing.com 2019-07-27

# Privacy Policy - Kapwing

Kapwing Inc. built the Kapwing website and app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Kapwing and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Information Collection and Use**

Users can explore the Sites, can view content, and can create new digital media using our tools without providing any personal information. Our Sites only collects personal information about a user if the user registers for Kapwing by signing In.

For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request is will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. These third party services are but may not be limited to the Facebook and Google OAuth login.

 **Log Data**

We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your device internal memory.

This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collection information and to improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

 **Service Providers**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

  * To facilitate our Service;
  * To provide the Service on our behalf;
  * To perform Service-related services; or
  * To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

 **Security**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **Links to Other Sites**

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

 **Children’s Privacy**

Kapwing is not a service directed towards children. Children under the age of 13 are not allowed to create an account on Kapwing account or otherwise use the website unless explicitly permitted by a parent. We support the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ( **COPPA** ), and our goal is to minimize the information gathered from and disseminated about kids under 13 while permitting them active access to creative tools. You must be over the age required by the laws of your country to create an account or otherwise use the Services, or we need to have obtained verifiable consent from your parent or legal guardian. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.

If a child creates an account using an authorized or managed Google or Facebook account, parents can review user data in My Account. Parents may also ask us to cease further collection of personal information from their children, or delete, the personal information we have collected online from their children, in which case, the child's account will be deleted. If a parent has any questions or concerns about his or her child's use of the Sites, we encourage the parent to contact us at hello@kapwing.com.

 **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
